impactguns.com 2019-09-23

# Privacy Policy

## Your Privacy Rights – Privacy Policy

At Impact Guns we are committed to protecting the privacy of our customers and users of our website located at www.impactguns.com (the "Site") . This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") gives you details of our privacy practices, including (a) what information we collect about you when you use the Site; (b) how the information will be used or disclosed; and (c) your rights with respect to our collection and use of your data. We may modify these policies from time to time and will provide notice of any major changes by posting such notice on the Site.

## What Information Do We Collect and Why?

Transaction Information: We may ask you to provide us with personal information on a voluntary basis in certain areas of the Site, and you will be required to provide personal information when you make purchases on the Site. The kinds of personal information that we may request may include your name, address, email address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services. All such information will be used in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

IP Addresses and "Cookie" Information: As is the case with many sites, the Site logs your IP address and uses standard technology called "cookies," which are small data files that are downloaded onto your computer when you visit the Site. Cookies automatically identify your browser to the impactguns.com server whenever you interact with the Site. We use cookies and the information they provide to improve our services and the quality of your experience with the Site. If you prefer not to allow us to collect "cookie" information, you can disable the cookies by turning them off in your browser, although some areas of the Site may not function properly if you do. We do not link IP addresses to any personally identifiable information. This means that your session will be tracked, but you will not be personally identified. However, certain kinds of cookies allow us to store certain information of yours so you can save time in filling out forms on the Site. We only send this type of cookie to your browser when you have provided your consent for us to save your profile information.

Web Beacons and Clear GIFs: The Site may also use pieces of code called "web beacons" or "clear gifs" to obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses the Site or when you are provided the opportunity to complete surveys, participate in a sweepstakes or other incentives, or open or respond to any newsletter or other email you may have received from the Site. These web beacons or clear GIFs may also be used to deliver cookies that conform to our cookie policy.

## How Else Does Impact Guns Use Information That It Collects from the Site?

As well as using information about you for the specific purposes set out above, we may also use information about visitors to the Site to monitor consumer interest in our range of products and services, to troubleshoot problems that may arise on our Site, to protect against fraud or other criminal activity on our Site, to customize your user experience on the Site, to notify you of product or service offerings that we think may be of interest to you, to inform you about special promotions, and to assist us in tailoring our product lines, our services, and the content of the Site to our online visitors' needs by collecting information about their preferences through tracking patterns of page-viewing on the Site. To assist in this, we might create a profile relating to you in order to show you the content that we think you might be interested in and to display the content according to your preferences. We may also share data we collect about you and other visitors to the Site in an anonymous or aggregated form with our business partners and others.

If you communicate with us, we may retain this correspondence to improve our products, services, and the Site, and for other disclosed purposes. We may use information you provide to us in order to send you updates, such as notifications of changes to the terms of our services or important information about our services and products.

Impact Guns may disclose information about individual users to third parties who provide services to Impact Guns and who agree to maintain the confidentiality of such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. These third parties provide a variety of services to Impact Guns, including, without limitation, fulfilling product orders, managing or hosting the Site, helping create new content and promotions for the Site, and sending or coordinating the sending of marketing communications to users who have consented to receive such materials. In situations where you have supplied your information in connection with a question or request for information about a product or service offered by one of our business partners, we may also send the information you have supplied to the business partners that offer such products or services.

Impact Guns will disclose information about individual users to governmental or judicial authorities or law enforcement agencies, or to other individuals or entities in response to a subpoena, court order, or other legal process. Further, Impact Guns may share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities or suspected fraud, or to enforce or apply the terms and conditions of our agreement.

If Impact Guns is acquired by or merged with another company, Impact Guns may transfer personally identifiable information about you to that company.

## Your Rights

Access and Correction: You have a right to know about the personal information that Impact Guns holds about you. You also have a right to correct, amend or delete such information if it is incorrect. If you wish to exercise these rights, please contact us by post or email at the address shown in the Contact Details section below.

Opt Out: From time to time, we may notify you of special promotions, changes to our Site, new product lines or new service offerings, or products that we think may be of special interest to you. If you decide you no longer want to be notified of this information, you may click on the “opt out” link in the associated email(s).

Mailing List: Impact Guns may occasionally share a portion of its mailing list with other reputable organizations. If you do not want your name and address shared with other organizations, or do not wish to receive our mailings, please contact us at 1-800-917-7137. You may also contact us online.

Please note that requested changes may take up to eight (8) weeks to take effect, particularly if we are removing your name from our postal mailings.

## Security

The Site incorporates appropriate safeguards to protect the security, integrity, completeness, accuracy and privacy of the personal information we have collected, and we have put in place reasonable precautions to protect information from loss, misuse, and alteration. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as required and only authorized individuals have access to the information you provide us. Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

You hereby acknowledge that Impact Guns is not responsible for any intercepted information sent via the Internet, and you hereby release us from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of intercepted information in any unauthorized manner.

## External Links

The Site provides links to various websites maintained by third parties. When you click on one of these links, you will be transferred out of our website and connected to the website of the organization or company that maintains such site. Even if an affiliation exists between our website and a third party website, we exercise no control over linked sites. Each of these linked sites maintains its own independent privacy and data collection policies and procedures. If you visit a website that is linked to the Site, you should consult that site's privacy policy before providing any personal information.

## Terms and Modifications to Privacy Statement

By using the Site, you signify your agreement to the terms of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with these terms, you should not use the Site. Impact Guns may modify this privacy statement at any time. If a material change is made to this Privacy Policy and/or the way we use our users' personally identifiable information, then we will post prominent notice of the nature of such change on the first page of this Privacy Policy and also on our home page. You are responsible for reviewing this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes to it. Your continued use of the Site indicates your assent to any changes to this Privacy Policy.

## Children

The Site is not directed to children, and Impact Guns does not knowingly solicit information from any child under the age of 18. Should a child whom we know to be under 18 send personal information to us, we will use that information only to respond directly to that child (or a parent or guardian) to inform him or her that we must have parental consent before receiving his or her personal information.

## Contact Details

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the privacy practices of the Site, or if you want to exercise any of the rights that you are given under this Privacy Policy, you can contact:

Impact Guns  
2710 S 1900 W  
Ogden, UT 84401
